<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">E - Gluu</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">E - Gluu</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Cold Calculated</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Add product</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Edit product</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Delete product</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="correo_electronico">Email</string>
    <string name="contraseña">Password</string>
    <string name="inciar_sesion">Log in</string>
    <string name="registrate_aqui">Register here</string>
    <string name="aun_no_tienes_cuenta">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="name_user">User</string>
    <string name="confirmar_contraseña">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="terminos">I accept the terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="registrate">Register</string>
    <string name="incia_sesion">Log in</string>
    <string name="yaregistrado">Are you register yet?</string>
    <string name="terminosycondiciones">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="appagregar">Add product</string>
    <string name="codigo">Bar code:</string>
    <string name="nombreproducto">Product name:</string>
    <string name="detalles">Product details:</string>
    <string name="stock">Stock:</string>
    <string name="preciocompa">Purchase price:</string>
    <string name="precioventa">Sales price:</string>
    <string name="agregar">ADD</string>
    <string name="appeliminar">Delete product</string>
    <string name="detalleselimnar">Press the button to scann your bar code</string>
    <string name="cerrarsesion">Log out</string>
    <string name="menu_scanner">Scanner</string>
    <string name="menu_map">Search Supplier</string>
    <string name="menu_lista">Product list</string>
    <string name="menu_detalles">Search Product</string>
    <string name="menu_terminos">Terms of service</string>
    <string name="up_nombrep">Product name</string>
    <string name="up_detallepro">Product details</string>
    <string name="up_preciocompra">Purchase price</string>
    <string name="up_precioventa">Sales price</string>
    <string name="up_stock">Stock</string>
    <string name="det_codigo">Insert product code</string>
    <string name="det_actualiza">Update product</string>
    <string name="det_busca">Search</string>
    <string name="del_txtview">Insert the code to be deleted</string>
    <string name="del_btnelim">Delete</string>
    <string name="del_hintcode">Code</string>
    <string name="menu_buscar">Search Product</string>
    <string name="menu_listap">Product list</string>
    <string name="menu_opciones">Additional options</string>
    <string name="menu_proveedor">Search Supplier</string>
    <string name="menu_otros">Other</string>
    <string name="scan_titulo">Scan bar code</string>
    <string name="scan_btn">Activate Scanner</string>
    <string name="scan_instruccion">Push the button to activate the scanner</string>
    <string name="scan_txtview">The scanned code will show up here</string>
    <string name="map_btn">Open Google maps</string>
    <string name="map_txtview">Push the button to start Google maps</string>
    <string name="ter_titulo">Terms of service</string>
    <string name="ter_body">" 1. These Terms and Conditions of Use regulate the rules to which the use of the APP \"E-GLUU\" is subject, which is made specifically for the company GLU of the APP attributes the condition of User to whoever does so and implies acceptance of all conditions included in this document and in the Privacy Policy and Legal Notice of said APP. The User should read these conditions each time he/she uses the APP, as they could be modified in the future. the Mexican legislation. For the resolution of any dispute relating to its interpretation or application, the User expressly submits to the jurisdiction of the courts of Mexico. Charges: You are responsible for payment of all costs or expenses you incur as a result of downloading and using the GLUU Application, including any carrier network or roaming charges. Please check with your service provider for details. Anonymous Statistics: GLUU reserves the right to track your activity on the GLUU Application and to report this to our third party statistical service providers. All of this is done anonymously. Protection of your personal information: We want to help you take all necessary steps to protect your privacy and information. Please refer to the GLUU Privacy Policy and Application privacy notices to learn what information we collect and the steps we take to protect your personal information. You may not alter or modify any part of the APP or its contents, circumvent, disable or otherwise tamper with (or attempt to circumvent, disable or tamper with) any security or other features of the program, or use the APP or its contents for any commercial or advertising purpose. It is prohibited to use the APP for the purpose of damaging property, rights or interests of GLUU or third parties. It is also prohibited to make any other use that alters, damages or disables the networks, servers, equipment, products and software of GLUU or third parties. 7. The APP and its contents (text, photographs, graphics, images, technology, software, links, content, graphic design, source code, etc.), as well as trademarks and other distinctive signs are the property of GLUU or third parties, the User not acquiring any right over them by the mere use of the APP. Subject to the conditions set out in the previous paragraph, GLUU grants the User a non-exclusive, free license to use the APP, for personal use, limited to the national territory and for an indefinite period of time. This license is also granted under the same terms with respect to updates and improvements made to the application. Such user licenses may be revoked by GLUU unilaterally at any time by simply notifying the User. 9. It is up to the User, in any case, to have adequate tools for the detection and disinfection of malicious programs or any other harmful computer element. GLUU is not responsible for any damage caused to computer equipment during the use of the APP. Likewise, GLUU shall not be liable for damages caused to Users when such damages are caused by failures or disconnections in telecommunications networks that interrupt the service. 10. IMPORTANT: We may, without any obligation to you, modify these Terms of Use without notice at any time. Your continued use of the App following any modification to these Terms of Use will constitute your acceptance of such modifications. If you do not accept these Terms of Use or agree to be bound by them, you must not use the App or download or use any related software. Your use of the App is at your sole risk. We have no responsibility or liability for the deletion or failure to store or transmit any content or other information maintained or transmitted by the App. We are not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any information or advice transmitted through the App. We may, at any time, limit or discontinue your use at our sole discretion. To the maximum extent permitted by law, in no event will we be liable for any related loss or damage. The User undertakes to make proper use of the APP, in accordance with the Law, with these Terms and Conditions of Use and with any other regulations and instructions that may be applicable. The User shall be liable to GLUU and to third parties for any damages that may be caused by breach of these obligations. These Terms and Conditions of Use are governed entirely by Mexican law. For the resolution of any dispute relating to their interpretation or application, the User expressly submits to the jurisdiction of the courts of Mexico."</string>
    <string name="redestitulo">Any question or doubt contact us! Our social networks are open</string>
    <string name="fbpage">Facebook Page</string>
    <string name="contacto">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="Sobrenosotros">About Us</string>
    <string name="equipo3">Team 3</string>
    <string name="contactanos">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="instapage">Instagram Page</string>
    <string name="telefono">Send a WhatsApp message to the number:</string>
</resources>